Hello guys how are you all in today's video
we are
making a complete parts video of TVS Entorq Race SP and
whatever parts you need in this video I will
tell you the complete details from the starting till the end so please do not skip this video
because if you skip then you will
not get to know the details of each and every part and whatever
parts I am telling you in this video will be
completely genuine parts from TVS
so guys let's start this video without any delay
and you are watching
baby
[Music]
we are going to talk first about the international one so
it will cost you ₹43
I will open it and show you,
you can also see its packing TVS has
done it very well
and you can see this
and this is LED headlight you can see
[Music] you can
see this gas this is of Race SP
and you can also see its packing you can see
this
and you can see its quality and its finishing it is
in complete glass finishing and
this sticker on top of it is
for plastic the company is like this  It provides
and if
I talk about its quality then it will cost you ₹3800 for one
piece
right now I am showing you the side panel as you
can see it
and whatever parts we are showing you in this video are
completely genuine parts you can
see it
and you can see its complete finishing and its details
and this is of the right side right now you
can see it on our website
and its price will be up to 3000 for the
side panel
and this is of the left side we have the right
side also available in stock and it will be
presented for
one side
we also have other colours available in it so
you can provide that too to you
and whatever parts I am showing you
we have many colour options
available in it in this video I am showing you the race
speed one, we have the inter
resurrection one, normal antoraca in it we
also have the captain America version
available whatever parts you want you
can directly whatsapp it you can see the description below
and you can see its quality and finishing
how well it is  This is this
and you can also see its back profile,
if I talk about its cost then it will cost
you 15-15s,
you know that we have
this available in stock on the side of the interior, I will
show this to you once,
you can see this is the side of the interior,
this trimmer for the right side is available with us
and we can also arrange for the left side
for you and
you can see its quality and finishing, it is
completely given in carbon fiber finishing by the
company
and if I talk about its pricing then
it will cost you 268
and it
remains in 3 months, so the price keeps changing from here, the
panel which is fitted under the seat of Race SP is
available with us in stock, I will make you
check that also once,
you can see this,
this is the part which is fitted in the portion and
you can also see the stickering on its side,
whatever I am showing you is from complete genuine parts
and you can also see its back side, there are
part numbers here also, all the
parts which I am showing you are of
part numbers  They come along because they are
general parts and
you can see its quality and fencing,
it comes in extreme model like this and if
I talk about its casting then
this photo will be 305
and this is its back profile,
it is available with us in stock
and you can see this is the side lock,
and
whatever you need for ignition also
comes along with it, it comes as a complete set
and if I talk about its casting
then it will cost you 1450,
now we will talk in detail about the types of inter
and if we talk about its tyre size then if I talk about 11
area then
its price will be 2400
and the front tyre and its
price will be 2200,
so please like this video and
share it with your friends and do not
go without subscribing to the channel
because it takes a lot of hard work to make this type of content
and if you need any of the parts shown in this video then I will
give you the number in the description, there you can directly call
or WhatsApp, the option of over India
delivery is also available with us.  You
can order directly from us, then
I will meet you in its next video, till then
I am here.